Коісні Іто

Singapore

koichi.ito@u.nus.edu https://github.com/koito19960406

☐ https://koichiito.com/

Research Interests

A PhD student at the National University of Singapore and consultant at the World Bank Group, interested in researching travel behavior, human perception, and equity with emerging spatial data sources, such as street-view imagery, and machine/deep learning techniques.

Education

The National University of Singapore

Aug 2022 - Present

Singapore

PhD in Urban Analytics

- Ongoing projects supervised by Dr. Filip Biljecki:
- 1. Python package for street view imagery analysis.
 - 2. EEG-based analysis of cyclists' visual perception.

The National University of Singapore

Aug 2019 - May 2021

Master of Urban Planning

Singapore

• 4.53/5.00 cumulative GPA (Highest Distinction)

Soka University of America

Aug 2015 - May 2019

Bachelor of Arts, Liberal Arts with Concentration in Environmental Studies

Aliso Viejo, CA

• 3.95 /4.00 cumulative GPA (summa cum laude)

Council on International Educational Exchange

Aug 2017 – Dec 2017

Study Abroad Program

Dakar, Senegal

Honors

•	Singapore	International	Graduate	Award	(SINGA)	Scholarshi	р
---	-----------	---------------	----------	-------	---------	------------	---

Aug 2022 - Present

• Japan Student Services Organization Scholarship (US\$40,000)

Aug 2020 - May 2021

• Soka University of America Makiguchi Scholarship (US\$10,000)

May 2019

• Soka University of America Dean's List (GPA is 3.7 or higher)

Dec 2015 - May 2019

• Soka University of America Merit Scholarship (US\$20,000)

Aug 2015 - May 2019

Publications

- Ito, K., Bansal, P., & Biljecki, F. (2024). Examining the causal impacts of the built environment on active transportation using time-series street view imagery. Manuscript under review for publication in Transportation Research Part A: Policy and Practice.
- Ito, K., Quintana, M., Han, X., Zimmermann, R., & Biljecki, F. (2024). Sidewalk the Talk: Translating street view imagery to correct perspectives to enhance bikeability and walkability studies. Manuscript under review for publication in Transportation Research Part C: Emerging Technologies.
- Ito, K., Kang, Y., Zhang, Y., Zhang F., & Biljecki, F. (2024). Understanding Urban Perception with Visual Data: A Systematic Review. Manuscript under review for publication in Cities.
- Hou, Y., et al. (Ito, K.) (2024). Global Streetscapes A comprehensive dataset of millions of street-level images over 700 cities for urban science and analytics. Manuscript under review for publication in ISPRS Journal of Photogrammetry and Remote Sensing.
- Wang, Z., et al. (Ito, K.) (2024). Mapping the landscape and roadmap of geospatial artificial intelligence (GeoAI) in quantitative human qeography: An extensive systematic review. International Journal of Applied Earth Observations and Geoinformation, https://doi.org/10.1016/j.jag.2024.103734
- Wang, Z., Ito, K., & Biljecki, F. (2023). Assessing the equity and evolution of urban visual perceptual quality with time series street view imagery. Cities, 145, 104704. https://doi.org/10.1016/j.cities.2023.104704
- Ito, K., & Biljecki, F. (2021). Assessing bikeability with street view imagery and computer vision. Transportation Research Part C: Emerging Technologies, 132, 103371. https://doi.org/10.1016/j.trc.2021.103371
- Biljecki, F., & Ito, K. (2021). Street view imagery in urban analytics and GIS: A review. Landscape and Urban Planning, 215, 104217. https://doi.org/10.1016/j.landurbplan.2021.104217

Academic Journal Peer Review

• Urban Informatics	Reviewed 2 times 2023, 2024
• Landscape and Urban Planning	Reviewed 2 times 2022, 2023
• International Journal of Geographical Information Science	Reviewed 1 time 2023
• Computational Urban Science	Reviewed 1 time 2023
• Journal of Geographical Systems	Reviewed 1 time 2022
• International Journal of Applied Earth Observation and Geoinformation	Reviewed 1 time 2022
• Environment and Planning B: Urban Analytics and City Science	Reviewed 2 times 2021 , 2022

Talks and Poster Presentations

•	"Advancing urban modeling with emerging geospatial datasets and AI technologies"	\mathbf{Feb}	2024
	Gave an invited talk at the Global Space and Technology Convention 2024 Conference hosted by Singapore	Land	
	Authority.	$Sing \epsilon$	apore

Gave a guest lecture talk at a GIS course at the National University of Singapore.

Singapore

"Sidewalk the Talk: Translating street view imagery to correct perspectives to enhance bikeshility and

• "Sidewalk the Talk: Translating street view imagery to correct perspectives to enhance bikeability and walkability studies"

Oct 2023

Presented a poster at the Urban Solutions and Sustainability R&D Congress.

Singapore

• "Street View Imagery: Have we answered all the questions with it? What's left to do?"

• "Application of GIS in research and international institution."

Oct 2021

Presented my research at Soka University of America, Advanced GIS Course.

Online

Work Experience

The World Bank Group — Poverty and Equity Global Practice

Organized a session at Spatial Data Science Symposium 2023.

• "Evaluating active mobility and urban perception with visual data"

Apr 2021 – Present

Oct 2023

Sep 2023

Online

Consultant

Remote

• Developed and maintained interactive data dashboards using Shiny and Golem frameworks to facilitate spatial data

- Developed and maintained interactive data dashboards using 5miny and Golem frameworks to facilitate spatial data visualization and analysis.
- Implemented spatial lag models in R to analyze factors correlated with poverty and stunting.
- Led the collection, cleaning, and mapping of various data sets including nighttime light, natural disaster metrics, household data, and accessibility indicators using R.
- Conducted a capacity-building program for the Tanzania's National Bureau of Statistics, imparting skills and knowledge on spatial analysis using R.

Johnson Controls Nov 2020 – May 2021

Data Analytics Intern

Singapore

- Constructed a data pipeline of PM2.5 data, weather data, and traffic data in Singapore on Azure Synapse for a real-time Power BI dashboard.
- Built a time-series model to predict PM 2.5 levels anywhere in Singapore in Python.

The World Bank Group — Tokyo Development Learning Center

Apr 2020 - Jan 2021

Urban Development Research Intern

Remote

- Compiled comprehensive data set of over 4,000 Tokyo-based startups' information, such as addresses, investors, and accelerators, using Python.
- Visualized financial performance of light rail transport system in Toyama prefecture between 2002 and 2019.

ENDA LEAD Afrique Francophone

Aug 2017 - Dec 2017

Research Intern

Dakar, Senegal

• Authored a report on accessibility to potable water in 500 villages in the Saint-Louis region in Senegal.

Teaching Experience

AR5805 Advanced Architecture Studio

Aug 2023 - Dec 2023

Teaching Assistant

The National University of Singapore, Department of Architecture

• Assisted the lead professor with logistical and administrative tasks, including the preparation of course documents and aiding in the smooth operation of lectures.

DEP5111 Planning Technologies

Jan 2024 - May 2024

Teaching Assistant

The National University of Singapore, Department of Architecture

• Assisted Master of Urban Planning students in mastering R Data Science through hands-on coding support, troubleshooting, and grading, enhancing their data analysis and visualization skills.

Supervising

• Zevu Wang: Master of Urban Planning, the National University of Singapore

Aug 2022 - May 2023

• Heyang Hua: Master of Urban Planning, the National University of Singapore

Jan 2024 - May 2024

Technical Skills

Languages: Japanese (native), English (fluent), French (limited working proficiency)

Computer Skills: Python, R, SQL, Spark, ArcGIS, QGIS, Google Earth Engine, Azure, AWS, Power BI

References

• Filip Biljecki

Presidential Young

(Assistant) Professor

College of Design and
Engineering, The National
University of Singapore

• Prateek Bansal
Presidential Young
(Assistant) Professor
College of Design and
Engineering, The National
University of Singapore

• Victor Mulas

Director

World Bank Group, Tokyo

Development Learning

Center

Takaaki Masaki
 Senior Economist
 The World Bank, Poverty
 & Equity Global Practice